在21世纪末，全球化学战争发生后
地球几乎完全无法可居住
居住空间成了最珍贵的资源
只有两个地域还可以住人
英国联邦
和殖民地
殖民地的工人每天
以唯一可用的交通工具
走遍地球每处，这工具就是
地心车
醒来，醒来
Wake up. Wake up.
醒来
Wake up.
我截断电源了
I cut the power.
我们大约有十秒时间
We've got about ten seconds
十秒后警钟便呜响
惊动整队人到来
before that alarm
brings an entire team down here.
来
Here.
- 我们要去了
- 好的，去
- We need to go.
- Okay, go.
去
Go.
好的，来
Okay, come on.
我爱你
I love you.
你现在告诉我？
You tell me now?
我爱你
I love you.
去！
Go!
不！不！不！
No!No!No!
我们去
Let go.
你现在就要去
You have to go now.
- 不，我不会离开你
- 我们去
- No. I won't leave you.
- Let go.
- 不
- 我答应会找你
- No.
- I promise I'll find you.
你要去
You have to go.
去！去！
Go! Go!
又发恶梦吗？
You have another nightmare?
是
Yeah.
宝贝，我们要怎样帮你？
Baby, what are we going to do with you?
我不知道
I don't know.
想谈谈你的梦吗？
Do you want to talk about it?
没有什么好谈的
There's nothing to talk about.
相同的梦吗？
Same dream?
相同的梦
Same dream.
相同的时间
Same time.
有人追捕我
I'm trapped, being chased.
我逃不掉
Can't get away.
接着我醒来
And then I wake.
就这么样吗？
And that's it?
只有你，没有其他人吗？
It's just you, nobody else?
不，只有我
No. Just me.
是因为我吗？
Is it me?
什么是你？
Is what you?
我不知道
I don't know.
只有你一人，你逃不了
You're alone. You can't get away.
是我们吗？
Is it us?
- 是我令你觉得受困吗？
- 不
- Do I make you feel trapped?
- No.
宝贝
Babe,
我知道我们
I know this isn't exactly
年轻时没有想过这事，但…
what we had in mind when
we were younger, but...
这堡垒？
This castle?
谁令我们幻想的一切成真了？
Who gets everything
they fantasize about, right?
我有了你
L 9011 you.
过来
Come here.
只不过是发梦罢了
It's just a dream. That's all it is.
知道吗？
Okay?
我们要令你发些好梦
Well, we're going to have to
get you some better dreams.
这不错呢
That would be nice.
来
Oh, come on.
紧急
- 该死
- 怎么了？
- Shit.
- What is it?
他们又炸英国联邦了
Another bombing in the U.F.B.
是载客火车
Passenger train.
该死的反动组织
Goddamn Resistance.
紧急医疗技术人员
我要赶搭六时半的班次离开
I'm going to have to
catch the 6:30 departure.
他们召集所有紧急人员上去
They're calling
all emergency personnel to go up top.
我要走了
I got to go.
我们今晚再继续，好吗？
We'll pick this up tonight, okay?
再睡一会
Try and get a little sleep.
我怕了睡觉
Sleep scares me.
梦见我吧
Well, dream of me.
好的
Okay.
但不要梦见我穿这裤子
But not in these pants.
乘客上车后不久便爆炸
The bomb went off just moments
after the commuters boarded.
火车遇袭突发新闻报导
据悉拯救队仍在搜索生还者
We are being told rescue teams
are still searching for survivors.
目前的死亡人数是144人
人数还在不断上升
The death toll is at 144 and still rising.
这是英国联邦在多月来第四次遇袭
This marks the fourth attack in United
Federation of Britain in as many months.
种种迹象均显示是
恐怖份子首领麦费思
And all signs point
to terrorist leader Matthias
和他的反动组织所为
and his Resistance movement.
英联剥削我们
The U. F.B. exploits us.
殖民地的工人应该获得平等待遇
The workers of The Colony deserve equality.
地心车将我们变成奴隶
The Fall enslaves us all.
高克根大臣以此证明
Chancellor Cohaagen
pointed to this as proof
麦费思不会以和平手段
that Matthias does not seek a peaceful path
争取殖民地独立
而是采取持久的血腥冲突
to independence for The Colony,
but rather a prolonged and bloody conflict.
英联的过剩人口不断上升
And with overpopulation
figures in the U. F.B. continuing to rise,
袭击偏偏在这个时候发生
this could not come at a worse time.
大家应该记得对上一次袭击
是在六星期前发生
You'll recall the last attack
occurred six weeks ago.
联邦警察一直指袭击是由
加路孝生发动的
Federal police have since attributed
that bombing to this man, Carl Hauser,
加路孝生是前情报人员
其后反叛
a former intelligence officer turned traitor
现在被视为麦费思的左右手
now considered to be
Matthias' right-hand man.
现时还没有消息得知
孝生跟今早的事件有何关系
No word yet as to whether Hauser
had a role in this morning's incident.
有地方要去吗？没有？
Going somewhere? No?
那么别让它妨碍你
Well, don't let that stop you.
那幻想还是永远无法成真吗？
That fantasy that remains
forever out of reach?
我们令幻想成真
不再无法成真了
Not anymore.
利高公司为你
At Rekall, we'll provide you
提供整套唯你独有的记忆
with a complete set
of memories all your own.
利高公司
Rekall.
我们为你记事
We can remember it for you.
利高公司
请各位乘客到指定的闸口报到
All passengers, please report
to your designated gates.
七时十五分开出的班次
最后召集乘客上车
This is the final boarding call
for the 7:15 departure.
面对事实吧！
Wake up to the truth!
高克根希望你满足现状
Cohaagen is counting on your complacency.
别让他们将你像牛羊般运到他方
Don't let them ship you
across the Earth like cattle.
来，走
Come on, move.
麦费思二真理
麦费思说的是真相！
Matthias speaks the truth!
地心车将我们变成奴隶！
The Fall enslaves us all!
地心车将我们变成奴隶
- 老友，你精神很差
- 所有A部门的班次都在第二层…
- Hey, buddy. You look like shit, man.
- All section A departures are located...
- 谢谢
- 没意板罪你
- Thanks.
- No offense.
我的精神是很差
你没有开罪我
I feel like shit. None taken.
我睡得不好，老友
I ain't sleeping so well, man.
新轮班时间也害得我好惨
Yeah, these new shifts
are kicking my ass, too.
至少加薪让我太太放心些
At least the extra pay
lets the missus rest easier.
看你
Look at you.
晨早六点只有半条人命
Mr. Glass-is-half-full at 6:00 a.m.
你好
Hola. Privyet.
欢迎到地心车
Welcome to The Fall.
上午七时二十一分
7:21 a.m.
往英国联邦的旅程需要十七分钟
Travel time to United Federation of Britain:
17 minutes.
还有六十秒便下堕
Dropping in 60 seconds.
有留意到
Has it ever occurred to you
我们总是坐同一个座位吗？
that we always sit in these exact same seats?
很多年了…为什么？
For years now... Why?
不知道
I don't know.
它们是座位，我们有屁股
They're seats. We have asses.
似乎是很合逻辑的事
Seems like the logical thing to do.
我是指我们永远依循相同的程序
I'm talking about us following
the same routine, all right,
日复日，年复年，从不质疑
day after day, year after year
without even questioning it.
想改变一下吗？
Want to switch it up?
易过借火
No sweat.
请大家离开座位前
Please make sure
all personal belongings are stored
将私人物品放在椅底
below your seat before departure.
噢
Oh, yeah.
这边更多事情发生
Much more happening on this side.
精明选择
Good call.
- 去你的
- 地心车开始下堕
- Dick.
- The Fall dropping in
四、三、二、一
four, three, two, one.
祝今天愉快
Have a nice day.
离开殖民地
到达英联
高克根谈清洗殖民地计划
Despite recent talks
between Chancellor Cohaagen
虽然高克根大臣
最近跟殖民地的总督谈过
and The Colony's governor,
但大臣宣布有鉴于今早的炸弹袭击
the Chancellor has announced
that he will be stopping
他会停止为殖民地提供所有人道援助
all humanitarian aid to The Colony
in light of this morning's bombing.
我致力清洗殖民地
As much as I want to focus our efforts
on cleaning up The Colony,
今天的恐怖袭击显示
today's terrorist attacks means that funding
我们需要将款项
用于加强联邦的机械警力
will have to go to bolstering
our synthetic federal police force.
我们永远以保护市民为先
The protection of our citizens
will always come first.
现正迈向地心
Approaching core.
预备反地心吸力
Please prepare for gravity reversal.
伊安法兰明
《铁金刚勇破海底城》
英国联邦
提升至三级保安
请先接受扫描
Security elevated to level three.
Please remain in scanners until cleared.
看来炸弹爆炸在这儿造成恐慌
Looks like that bomb set off
a hell of a panic up here.
请准备好身份证明文件
在进入筛查区之前
Identification documents must be in hand
and ready to present to the security officer
向保安人员出示
before entering the screening area.
所有工厂人员必需
通过十二号保安闸
All factory personnel must enter
through security gate 12.
唏，你对利高公司有何认识？
Hey, what do you know about Rekall?
- 替人改变脑袋的那鬼东西吗？
- 是
- That mind-altering shit?
- Yeah.
杜格，我劝你别惹他们
Do yourself a favor, Doug,
stay away from them.
为什么？
Why is that?
记得第三班有个戴维思吗？
Remember Travis from shift three?
- 戴维思
- 他在婚前光顾利高公司
- Travis.
- Went to Rekall for his bachelor party.
他想成为火星之王或什么的
Wanted to be king of Mars or some shit.
我也想去火星
I'd like to go to Mars.
他接受叶切断术
Got himself lobotomized.
任何有关生物识别技术…
Any available biometric tech,
please report to the...
- 你信这些故事？
- 向总办事处报告
- You believe those stories?
-...central office...
- 利高公司的故事？
- 是
- About Rekall?
- Yeah.
是的，我信
Yeah, I do.
来
Come on.
你从不想这个吗，只想一点儿？
You never thought about it, just a little bit?
我不需要想它
I don't need to think about it.
别胡思乱想
Don't mess with your mind, man.
不值得呢
It ain't worth it.
好吧，听好
All right, all right, listen up.
也许我需要胡思乱想
Maybe I need my mind messed with.
我们又开始轮双班了
We're starting double shifts again.
唏！唏，唏，唏
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey-
- 别怪我
- 弊
- Don't blame me.
- Fuck me.
我跟你一样不想待在这儿
知道吗？
I don't want to be here
any longer than you do, okay?
因为今早的事件
They've increased
the production of police synthetics
他们增加了机械警察的生产量
所以…
thanks to that shit this morning, so...
向高克根大臣
So take all your complaints
投诉吧
to Chancellor Cohaagen.
你们这班殷实的混蛋之中
Now, which one of you
fine, upstanding assholes
有谁想训练新人？
wants to train the new guy?
来
Come on.
唏
Hey.
来
Come on.
别看着我
Don't look at me.
你最后炒的那个是我训练的
I trained the last guy you fired.
- 葛特
- 是
- Quaid.
- Yeah.
你升级
You're up.
- 很好，多谢
- 别客气
- Great. Thank you.
- Any time.
机械警察下来了！
Synthetics coming down!
第三部份的焊接扫描器
暂停使用
Section three weld scanners are
temporarily offline.
别那样扶着
Don't hold it like that.
扶这儿
Hold it here.
扶着那儿会短路的
If you hold it there and the synth shorts,
会有螺栓射穿你的手
one of those bolts
will shoot straight through your hand.
不是说笑的，知吗？
No Shit, huh?
不是说笑的
No shit.
要赚取一天假不难呢
Easier ways to get a day off.
谢谢
Thanks.
你的朋友错了
Hey, you know, your friend
was wrong, by the way.
关于利高公司
About Rekall.
你做了吗？
What, you've done it?
已经三次了
Been three times already.
真的吗？
Really?
我有史以来最美妙的回忆
Best memories I have.
比这个好得多
A whole lot better than this shit.
唏
Hey.
找阿麦吧
Ask for Mac.
知吗？你会高兴得感谢我
Okay? You're going to thank me.
第9层，请向厂方报到
Level nine,
please report to Human Resources.
醒定些，这家伙不好惹
Strap yourself in.
This guy's a laugh-a-minute.
下一位
Next.
你来了，请坐
Here you are. Please, have a seat.
你在生产线工作
You work on the production line.
是，在启动组
In activation, yeah.
我知你住在殖民地
I understand you live in The Colony.
是，我像所有人一样坐车来
Yeah, I make the commute
like everyone else.
对不起，你是谁？
Sorry, who are you?
If you don't mind my asking.
- 我属于高克根行政部
- 明白
- I'm with the Cohaagen administration.
- I see.
现在政局紧张，我们高度关注
Given these politically charged times,
there is a heightened concern regarding the,
我们员工的忠诚
shall we say, loyalty of our workers.
- 但我不是为你工作
- 但你是
- Yeah, but I don't work for you.
- But you do.
这公司获批政府的机械警察合约
This company was granted
the government contract for police synths,
而我们是政府
and we are, the last time I checked,
the government.
我明白了
你叫我来是因为我居住的地方
Okay, I see. So you brought me in here
because of where I live.
我们叫所有员工来
We're bringing in all the employees.
真的？谁会问行政人员？
Oh, really? Who's questioning the suits?
谁会问你？
Who gets to question you?
葛特先生
Mr. Quaid,
你的工作可以接触
机械警察技术的机密
in your capacity here, you are privy to police
synth technology that is currently classified.
我知道怎样开着它们
I know how to turn 'em on,
if that's what you mean.
我们希望你签字
We'd like you to sign this.
这是什么？
And what is that?
确认你不会泄露专有技术
It affirms that you will not
divulge proprietary technology
不向国内国外任何人泄露
to any source, either foreign or domestic.
和你没有参加
And that you are not actively engaged
任何企图推翻这个政权的活动
in any attempt to overthrow
this administration.
你想我签纸说我不是恐布份子？
You want me to sign something
that says I'm not a terrorist?
这份文件只是确认你自称的身份
The document merely affirms
you are who you say you are.
如果我是恐布份子
And if I were a terrorist,
你以为它会令我供出来？
you think this would make me tell you?
- 这是你们的伟大计划？
- 葛特先生…
- Is that your guy's big plan?
- Mr. Quaid...
你们捉到人未？
You catch anyone yet?
我今日还要见75个人
I have 75 more of these interviews today.
你知嘛？我今日工作得好累
Yeah, you know what, pal?
I had a long day, too.
如果你想再有工作，收声和照办
Well, if you'd like to have another,
you'll shut up and do what you're told.
晔
Wow.
第二页下面
Second page at the bottom.
你喜欢你的工作？
You like your job?
我喜欢和人接触
I'm a people person.
多谢
Thank you.
下一位
Next.
九至十八号闸现已关闭
Gates nine through 18 now closed.
A部门的班次在40…
Section A departures will reopen in 40...
累了一整天了，去睡吧
发个甜梦 - 吻与拥抱
终于了
All right, finally.
- 为健康干杯
- 天啊
- Cheers. Salud.
- Yeah. Jesus.
唏，老友
Hey, buddy.
- 唏
- 怎么样？
- Hey.
- Glad you called.
我好点了
Needed a drink.
罗莉今晚要工作吗？
Lori working tonight?
是
Yeah.
唏，梅利，例牌
Hey, Murray. Same.
有学过弹钢琴吗？
You ever learn how to play the piano?
我一直想学弹
Yeah, I always wanted
to learn to play the piano.
你今天怎么了？
What's with you today?
什么？
What?
不单止是为了升职的事吧
Yeah, exactly.
你今天心不在焉
You've been zoned out all day.
我老是发那些梦
I've been having these dreams.
梦？
Dreams?
对，我觉得
Yeah, feels
我在做一些事情…
like I'm doing something...
一些事情…
Something...
一些要紧的事情
一些重要的事情，知道吗？
Something that matters,
something important, you know?
不，不大知道
Nope, not so much.
你认为我们做的工作不重要吗？
You don't think what we do is important?
的确？来，哈利
Really? Come on, Harry.
我们老远来到做无聊的工作
We commute halfway
around the world for shit jobs,
人工又低，来这鬼酒吧
喝这些鬼酒喝至大醉
for shit pay, to come to this shit bar
and get drunk on too much shit beer.
- 梅利，我无意冒犯
- 唔
- No offense, Murray.
- Yeah.
什么？你真的很满意你的生活吗？
What? Are you actually happy
with how your life's turned out?
- 我为什么要？
- 你是认真的？
- Why the hell shouldn't I be?
- Are you serious?
我的生活有什么不妥吗？
Is there something wrong with it?
没有，知道吗？你说得对
算了吧
No. You know what? You're right. Forget it.
我只是…
I'm just...
算了吧
Forget it.
那女孩是谁？
Who's the girl?
你说什么？
What do you mean?
你听见的，那女孩是谁？
You heard me. Who's the girl?
没有女孩，只是我的问题
There's no girl. It's just me.
好
Good.
因为像罗莉这样的女人不易找
'Cause women like Lori
don't just fall out of the sky.
你很幸运
You're a lucky man.
你的生活是我梦寐以求的
You're living the dream, my friend.
- 真的？
- 真的
- Really?
- Yeah, man.
- 梦寐以求？
- 是
- I'm living the dream?
- Yeah.
好吧，老兄，明天见
All right, big guy. Tomorrow.
唏
Hey.
想听我的意见吗？
My advice?
说吧
Go ahead.
及早想法子解决你面对的问题
Figure out a way to deal with
whatever the hell it is you're going through
以免它毁了你的一生
before you mess your shit up for good.
我可能喝得太多了
It's possible I might have drank too much.
哈利，可能是吧
Yeah, it's possible, Harry.
我想吐
I'm going to go throw up on something now.
- 好的
- 之后你会回复理性
- Okay.
- And you're going to get your shit together
然后回家，听见吗？
and go home to your wife, you hear me?
哈利，我想人人都听见你了
Yeah, I think everyone heard you, Harry.
杜格，晚安
Night, Dougie.
晚安
Good night.
你像在找什么似的
Seem like you're looking for something.
是这个吗？
Is it this?
怎样都可以
Anything goes here.
相信我，你会恨不得有三只手
Trust me, baby,
you're gonna wish you had three hands.
我在找利高公司
I'm looking for Rekall.
你知道在哪儿吗？
You know where I can find it?
到天堂的阶梯，在那边
Stairway to heaven, over there.
利高公司
我无法改变你的想法？
我很互动的
Sure I can't change your mind?
I'm a lot more interactive.
相信是
I bet.
谢谢
Thank you.
欢迎光临利高公司
Welcome to Rekall.
第一次惠顾吗？
First time?
对，很明显，对？
Yeah. That obvious, huh?
很好
It's fine.
没有什么好怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of.
这儿很安全
This is a safe place.
我的朋友马力给我这名片
他叫我找阿麦
My friend Marek gave me this card,
told me to ask for Mac.
- 他在里面
- 谢谢
- He's right inside.
- Thanks.
请尽兴
Remember to have a good time.
欢迎
Welcome.
唏
Hey.
你是马力的朋友
You're a friend of Marek's.
是
Yes.
我们一起工作
Yeah, we work together.
就是那个吗？
Is that it?
就是这个
That is it.
感觉很真实的吗？
And it feels like real life?
生活只是脑袋
对所见事物的化学认知？
What is life but our brain's
chemical perception of it?
脑袋对你眼所见的产生化学反应
Your eyes see, your brain chemistry reacts.
我们只是删除中间媒体
直接产生化学作用
Here, we just remove the middleman
and we go straight to the chemistry.
真实感会稍逊吗？
Does that make it any less real?
幻象不管多真实终归都是幻象
An illusion, no matter how convincing,
is still just an illusion.
很好
That's very good.
客观来说你是对的
You're right, objectively.
但从内心来说
But from the inside,
主观上…
subjectively...
我可以保证，情况是完全相反
I assure you, it's quite the opposite entirely.
我明白了
Listen, I get it.
I get it.
你在这里因为你觉得缺少了什么
You're here because
you feel like something's missing.
你受到牵引，想对什么知多一点
You got some tug, some longing
for something more.
我们会令你如愿
We're going to give you that thing.
是吗？
Is that right?
那可能是你永远无法办到的
Could be something
you could never afford to do.
可能是你一直想尝试
但又从来不敢尝试的秘密
Something secret you've always wanted
to try, but you would never, ever dare.
你说的秘密是什么意思？
What do you mean, secret?
什么都可以
Anything.
说出你的幻想
我们便会给你回忆
Tell us your fantasy.
We'll give you the memory.
你想富有出名吗？
You want to be rich and famous?
想受千万人崇拜吗？
Worshiped by millions?
或者是更刺激的事情吗？
Maybe something
with a little more adrenaline, huh?
罪恶克星？世界级运动员？
Crime fighter? Or world-class athlete?
密探，很适合你，是吗？
Secret agent. That's you. Right?
秘密银行帐户
Clandestine bank accounts,
- 密码讯息
- 密探
-coded messages.
- Secret agent.
我可以办到
I could do that.
对，是密探
Yeah, as an intelligence operative.
你可能为反动组织工作
You could be working for the Resistance.
你可能为高克根工作
Maybe you work for Cohaagen.
为何限死白己？
为何不是为两者工作？
Or why limit yourself? Why not both?
杜格，最后
One last thing, Doug.
要让你彻底明白
As a matter of full disclosure,
你选的秘密生活元素全都是不真实的
none of the secret life elements
you chose can actually be true.
很多人
See, the thing is, a lot of guys
到这里来，想在现实生活以外
come in here, they want
the secret mistress trip
多一位秘密情人
when they already have one,
a real one, on the side.
这点我们办不到
We can't do that.
这会构成无法弥补的冲突和混乱
It would cause
irreparable conflict and confusion.
这会令大脑崩溃
That's how brains get blown.
别担心，我没有任何秘密
Don't worry, I don't have any secrets.
我肯定你没有
只是以防万一
I'm sure you don't, but just in case,
我们必需为你进行身心状况检查
we're going to run
a psycho-polygraphic panel on you anyway.
马格思，动手
Marcus, go.
特务 - 档案：94422686
你会享受其中
You're going to have such a good time,
不想回来
you're not going to want to come back.
看
Look at that.
看来你太太有个爱慕者
Looks like your wife
does have a man who appreciates her.
这点没有冲突
No conflict there.
对不起，目前这还是
将化学物质注入人体的最佳方法
Sorry. Still the best way
to get chemicals into the human body.
好的
All right.
我们开始
Let's get this show on the road.
准备拯救世界
Get ready to save the world.
老友，顺风
Happy trails, man.
稍后你可以把情况告诉我…
You can tell me all about it when you get...
等等
Wait.
什么？
What?
该死
Shit.
该死？怎么了？有什么不妥？
Shit? What is it? What's wrong?
在药力发作前把针拔掉
Yank that needle out before it takes.
是什么？有什么不妥？
What is it? What's wrong?
- 你说谎
- 说什么谎？
- You lied.
- Lied about what?
- 混蛋
- 我没有情妇
- Son of a bitch.
- Look, I don't have a mistress.
- 你在说什么
- 情妇？
- What are you talking about?
- Mistress?
你是间谍
You're a goddamn spy.
生命征状不稳定
Vitals are everywhere.
你来这里干吗？为什么？
Why are you here? Why?
联邦警察！
Federal police!
- 联邦警察！站起来！
- 不，等等
- Federal police! On your feet now!
- No, wait!
你们搅错了！全都…
This is all a mistake! It's all...
我是普通人
I'm nobody.
- 我是普通人
- 举手！
- I'm nobody.
- Hands on your head now!
好的
Okay.
转身！
Turn around!
好
Okay.
该死
Holy shit.
118.5，代码6
105北…
118.5, code six. 105 north...
去
Go!
走
Move, move, move!
联邦警察！
Federal police!
第一组
Team one, have you
你捉到疑犯了吗？
secured the suspect?
第一组，答话
告诉我你那边发生什么事
Team one, advise.
Let me know what's going on in there.
史提芬，拍摄情况
Stevens, get an eyeball in there now.
该死，全都死了
Shit. They're all down.
他单独行动！
He's all alone!
破门
Let's punch it.
上锁
退后！退后！
Fall back! Fall back!
守着出口！
Cover the exit!
在当局形容为恐怖袭击的事件中
In what is being described
利高公司大堂枪击事件
证实20人死亡
as a terrorist attack,
a solitary gunman opened fire
一名独行枪手在位于
费蒙市中心的利高公司大堂
向一队联邦警员开火
on a squadron of federal police
at the Rekall Lounge in downtown Fremont.
我们仍在等候
We are still awaiting word
- 公布确实的伤亡数字
- 是
-on precisely how many casualties there are.
- Yes.
- 但官员现在确定…
- 好的
- But officials now confirming...
- Okay.
…至少有20名警员被枪杀…
...that at least 20 officers have been killed...
杜格，天
Oh, my God, Doug.
我明白
I understand. Yeah.
- 谢谢
- 罗莉
- Thank you.
- Lon.
- 你在这里真好
- 我当然在这里
- I'm so glad you're here.
- Of course I'm here.
我担心得要死
I've been going out of my mind.
你到哪里去了？
Where have you been?
看，有事发生了
Look, something bad has happened.
不，我知，我刚才接到电话
No, I know. I just got the call.
我们全都要随时候命
We've all been put on standby.
你不明白
You don't understand.
什么？
What?
天
Oh, my God.
杜格，你没事吧？
Doug, are you okay?
罗莉，不是反动份子杀那些警卫的
Lori, it wasn't the Resistance
who killed those sentries.
不是恐怖份子
It wasn't terrorists.
是我
It was me.
你什么？
What was you?
罗莉，是我杀他们的
Lori, I'm the one who killed them.
你杀了20名持枪的人？
You killed 20 armed men?
不，只是10个
No. No, it was more like ten.
但你杀了他们吗？
But you killed them?
你用什么杀人，用书吗？
With what, honey, your book?
- 罗莉，我说真的
- 杜格，你吓怕我了！
- Lori, look, I'm serious.
- Doug, you're scaring me!
对不起
I'm sorry.
听来真疯狂？
This is going to sound crazy, okay?
下班后我去了利高公司
I went to Rekall after work.
- 那么…
- 什么？
- And. ..
- What?
- 他们对你做了什么？
- 什么都没有
- What did they do to you?
- Nothing.
什么都没有
我坐在椅上，他们替我接上仪器
Nothing.
I sat in the chair, they hooked me up.
他们什么都未做警方便冲进来
Before they could do anything,
the police burst in.
他们想抓我
They tried to take me.
我自然地反应
And I just reacted.
杀了他们
And I killed them.
杜格，听好，你没有杀人
Listen, you didn't kill anyone, Doug.
相信我，全都是我杀的
Trust me, I killed everyone.
不，甜心，你不明白吗？
No, sweetheart, don't you see?
你以为自己做过什么都跟这个无关
Whatever you think you did
had nothing to do with any of this.
那些混蛋干扰你的脑袋
Those assholes screwed with your mind,
你出现偏执幻觉
and now you're having some
kind of a paranoid delusion.
那些地方真的很危险
Those places are really dangerous.
不论发生了什么事
我们都会安然渡过
Whatever it is that happened,
we're going to get through it.
过来，来
Come here. Come on.
来
Come on.
来得太突然了
It happened so fast.
没事的，我们可以解决
It's okay, we'll figure it out.
模拟疑犯样貌
特别报告
疑犯仍然在逃
对不起
I'm sorry.
罗莉，我无法呼吸
Lori, I can't breathe.
来
Come on.
你做什么？
What the hell are you doing?
罗莉，怎么…
Lori, what the fuck...
Lori, what the...
罗莉，你做什么？
Lori, goddamn it, what are you doing?
执行职务
My Job.
你疯了吗？
Are you crazy?
我疯了吗？
Am I crazy?
杜格，问得好
That's a good one, Doug.
考虑到你根本不知道你是谁
Considering you don't even know
who the hell you are.
你真的以为一个工厂工人可以
Do you really believe
a factory worker could take out
干掉多名受过精密训练的人员吗？
an entire room of highly-trained men?
告诉我发生什么事
Tell me what is going on.
说呀！
Talk!
也许我们直截了当说
“直至死亡把我们分辟”
Or we can skip straight to
"Until death do us part."
我不是你太太
I'm not your wife.
一派胡言，我们结婚七年了
That's bullshit.
We've been married seven years.
我是英联国际刑警
被派来扮作你太太
I'm U.F.B. police intel,
assigned to play your wife.
六星期前，我根本不认识你
Six weeks ago, I didn't even know you.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
是真的
It's true.
你的记忆给抹掉了
他们替你植入
Your memory was erased,
your mind was implanted
你以为过了一辈子过的生活
with a life you think you've lived.
宝贝，明白吗？
You keeping up, baby?
根本从来没有一个
叫杜格拉斯葛特的人
There is no Douglas Quaid, there never was.
你是说我不…
Are you saying I don't...
这…
This...
每个…我们的婚姻…
Every... Our marriage...
我怎么说？我扮妻子很出色
What can I say? I give good wife.
来
Come on.
你心内的确相信
Deep down, did you really believe
像我的这类人会下嫁这类人
someone like me
would marry someone like you,
住在这个鬼地方吗？
live in this shithole?
若我不是这个我，那么我是谁？
If I'm not me, then who the hell am I?
我怎知道？
How would I know?
我只是在这里执行职务
I just work here.
推测吧
Speculate.
若要我猜
If I had to guess,
因为高克根要用尽方法将你藏起来
不让反动份子发现你
all the trouble Cohaagen's taken
to hide you from the Resistance,
你一定是颇重要的
you must be fairly important.
加上你的技艺
我想你绝不可能是他的园丁
And with your skill set, I think it's highly
doubtful you're his gardener.
高克…
Cohaa...
高克根要将我藏起来
Cohaagen's trying to hide me?
为什么你想杀我？
Why are you trying to kill me?
说呀！
Talk!
杜格，就当是七年之痒吧
Call it seven-year itch, Doug.
况且你根本没有看见我想杀你！
And by the way, you haven't even
begun to see me try to kill you!
不！
No!
该死
Shit.
第三组，出动
Team three, break position.
我需要你到现场
I need you on-site now.
火车27，明白
Glide two seven, understood.
该死
Shit.
行动！
Move!
该死
Shit.
我想将他的电话再次连网
I want his phone back on the grid now.
唏
Hey!
行动！
Move!
喂
Hello?
Hello.
我是夏文
It's Hammond.
我不认识叫夏文的人
I don't know any Hammond.
该死
Oh, shit.
你说过这情况可能会发生
You said this might happen.
去找一块玻璃
Look, find a piece of glass.
找到了把手放上去
Put your hand to it.
马上去
Do it now.
哦，天呐
Oh, Jesus.
他们真的对你进行了大工程
They really did a number on you, didn't they?
你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
你真的什么都记不起吗？
You honestly don't remember
any of it, do you?
记不起
No. No, I don't.
记起什么？你怎么会认识我？
Remember what? How do you know me?
我们以前一起当联邦国际刑警
We worked at federal intel together.
我们时间无多
Look, there isn't much time.
你对我说过若你再次出现在网络上
You said to me
that if you ever pop back on the grid,
我便得挂这个电话号码
I was to phone this number.
网络？
The grid?
你的电话
Your phone.
被重新启动
It's been reactivated.
你以为他们是怎样追踪你的？
How do you think
they've been tracking you?
你叫过我给你传讯息
Look, you asked me to give you a message,
所以我现在传给你
去拿锁匙
so I'm giving it to you. Get the key.
锁匙？什么锁匙？
The key? What is the key?
你说过你会知道
You said you'd know.
我不知！告诉我那是什么
Yeah, well, I don't! So tell me what it is.
我知道我们以前很熟落
Look, I know we were close,
但情况太危险了
but this is getting too dangerous.
若他们知道我跟你联络过，我会…
If they find out I've contacted you, I'll be...
只请…只请告诉我发生什么事
Just... Just tell me what's going on.
好吧，你想我是谁？
All right, who is it you think I am?
夏里
Henry.
夏里，好的，什么夏里？
Henry, okay, good. Henry, who?
时间无多了
Look, there isn't any time.
若我是你，我会扔掉那电话
If I were you, I'd get rid of that phone.
- 好吧？现在
- 我如何可以扔掉那电话？
- All right? Now.
- How can I get rid of the phone?
它在我的手里，我如何…
It's in my goddamn hand. How am I...
唏，等等
Hey, wait.
一个新讯息
第一银行
保险箱10549
10549 , 10549
10549. 10549.
来
Come on.
该死
Holy shit.
怎么了？
What is that?
我可以怎样弄来一个？
Where can I get one?
- 怎么了？
- 来
- What the hell?
- Yo, come on.
辨明追踪者
唏，机械怪，那是我的！
Hey, Robo-dick, that's mine!
有地方要去吗？没有？
Going somewhere? No?
那么别让它妨碍你
Well, don't let that stop you.
那幻想还是永远无法成真吗？
That fantasy that remains
forever out of reach?
不再无法成真了
Not anymore.
利高公司为你提供
整套唯你独有的记忆
At Rekall, we'll provide you with
a complete set of memories all your own.
利高公司
Rekall.
我们为你记事
We can remember it for you.
进来！我们为你们准备了热的食物
Come inside! We have hot food for you.
葛特一定知道我们一直在跟踪他
Quaid must've known we'd be tracking it.
他到底怎么会知道的？
How the hell would he have known that?
该死
Oh, shit.
他令你像呆子
He made you look like a fool.
长官，他接受过密集追踪训练
He'd had major tactical training, sir.
你们没有告诉我
I wasn't made aware of that.
他怎么会发现的？
How the hell did he get activated?
一名执行此任务的特工告诉我
他到过利高公司
An agent in place
told me he'd gone to Rekall.
我派了一组人去
但他们下手前他的记忆已被毁
I sent a team in, but his memory implant
had been blown before they could get to him.
我比他迟了十五分钟
I'm 15 minutes behind him.
只是废止，明白吗？
Neutralize only, do you understand me?
别杀死他
No lethal force.
我要留活口再植入
I want him alive for re-implantation.
长官，他到底是谁？
Who the hell is this guy, sir?
别让人看见我的脸孔
Take me off display.
电话线安全
Line is secure.
你开我玩笑吗？
Are you fucking kidding me?
为何他还活着？
Why is he still alive?
长官，是
Yes, sir.
- 我们一见到他会马上杀掉
- 但大臣先生说…
- We kill him on sight.
- But the Chancellor said...
对不起，你说什么？
I'm SOFTY, say again?
- 对不起
- 大臣先生不在
- Sorry.
- The Chancellor's not here
此现实世界
on the ground.
相信我，若那目标有半个机会
他也会干掉我们
Believe me, if that target's given
even half a chance, he will end us.
若你见到他，你要杀掉他
If you see him, you shoot to kill.
- 明白吗？
- 走开好吗，混蛋？
- Is that understood?
- Will you lay off, asshole?
我一直告诉你那是我的电话
I keep telling you, that's my phone.
是那人给我的，我发誓
The guy gave it to me, I swear.
他去哪？
Where was he going?
谁？
Who?
给你电话的那人
The man that gave it to you.
小姐，我像有异能的人吗？
我怎么知道？
Lady, do I look like a psychic?
How the hell do I know?
我只能说这电话现在是我的财物
好了吗？
All I'm saying is that phone
is my personal property now, okay?
我晓得自己的权利，所以你们可以…
I know my rights, so you all can just...
唏
Hey!
你回气之后
When you've got your breath back,
要如实对我说出那男人对你说的一切
you're going to tell me everything
从头开始说起
that man said to you,
starting from the beginning.
你是谁？
Who are you?
他的太太
I'm his wife.
新亚洲第一银行
好，你没事
Okay. You're good.
先生，我有什么可以效劳？
Can I help you, sir?
我在这里开了保险箱
Yeah, I have a safety-deposit box here.
编号是10549
It's 10549.
好的
Okay.
这边
This way, please.
签名对就可以了
Just need a signature match.
- 签名对？
- 账户的
- Signature match?
- For the account.
有问题吗？利特先生
Is there a problem, Mr. Reed?
不，没问题
No. No problem.
你用任何一个客户室都可以
You can use any one of these client rooms.
我就在外面
需要我的话随时叫我
And I'll just be outside, if you need me.
谢谢
Thanks.
夏文查尔思 - 殖民地556区
13楼 - M - NeAs
周健 - 殖民地512区
利特夏里 - 英联E14区
13楼 - M - NeAs
收到一个资料档
好
Okay.
他们随时会来捉我
They're gonna be
coming for me any second,
所以我要快点
so I need to make this quick.
好的，你会无法置信
Okay, you're going to
find this hard to believe,
但你不是你以为自己是的那个人
but this is not your face.
我被捕和整容
I've been captured and resculpted into this,
变成你以为自己是的那个人
this person you think you are now.
若你现在看着
即表示我当时逃不了
If you're watching this,
it means I failed to escape.
即是他们成功给你
It means, it means they
succeeded in giving you
新的名字和身份
a new name, a new identity
还有新的记忆…
什么都换了新的
and a new set of memories...
Everything, everything.
你对自己生活的一切所想所知
Anything you think
you know about your life,
都不是真的
it's not real.
你要相信我
You have to believe me.
现在你要做的最重要事情
The most important thing for you to do now,
是去我的寓所！
is get to my apartment!
去我的寓所！
Get to my apartment!
地址是夏士普伦街549号D座
549 Hysperion, Block D.
我想告诉你更多
但现在还不能信任你
I want to tell you more,
but I can't trust you yet.
我唯一希望的是
若你是我
My only hope is, if you are me,
你会找到锁匙
你会知道怎样做
you found the key
and you know what to do with it.
你找到锁匙便会知道怎样做！
You found the key
and you know what to do with it!
什么锁匙？什么锁匙？
What key? What key?
- 什么锁匙？
- 祝好运
- What key?
- Good luck.
- 老友，祝好运
- 什么…
- Good luck, buddy.
- What...
资料档已加密
来，来
Come on, come on.
来
Come on.
资料档已加密
无法传递
请乘客前往接受保安筛查
Passengers may proceed
to security screening.
请准备好身份证明文件
Please have
your identification documents ready.
等等！
Hold it!
先生，请再走过扫描器
Sir, I'm gonna have to ask you to step
through the scanner again, please.
你在这里多久了？
How long are you here?
两星期
Two weeks.
是殖民地的市民吗？
Are you a citizen of The Colony?
是
Yes.
打算逗留多久？
How long is your stay?
三天
Three days.
你来英联做什么的？
What is your business in the U.F.B.?
谢谢
Thank you.
对不起？
Excuse me?
三天
Three days.
是，谢谢
Yes. Thank you.
- 是他！
- 怎么…
- That's him!
- What the...
大家伏下！
Everybody down!
东面出口！
Eastside exit!
去
Go, go, go!
我们看见疑人！
We have a visual!
- 过来！
- 走！
- Coming through!
- Go, go!
已经通知外面各个单位戒备
We've alerted all units outside.
为何他带着武器也可以通过扫描器？
How the hell did he get
a weapon past the scanner?
他没有
He didn't.
好极
Perfect.
走，走，走
Move, move, move, move!
让开！走！
Clear, clear! Move!
- 6246戒备
- 唏！
- Alert 6246.
- Hey!
所有单位就绪
All units, take position.
- 他朝I-19方向走了
- 收到
- He's headed up to I-19.
- Copy that.
开动！
Move it!
天啊
Oh, God! Oh, God.
马上进去！
Get in! Now!
真无法相信是你
I can't believe it's you.
你认得我吗？
You recognize me?
不知道
I don't know.
等等
Wait.
你知道我是谁吗？
Do you know who I am?
我到处找你
I have been looking for you everywhere.
突然你在所有警方扫描器中出现
Suddenly, you show up
on all the police scanners.
该死
Oh, shit.
等等
Hold on.
你真的记不起我吗？
You really don't remember me?
记不起
No.
我以前见过你，但…
I've seen you before, but it's...
不要紧
It's okay.
不要紧，我会向你说明一切
It's okay. I can explain everything.
中央99，空援人员发现
Central 99, air support has visual
疑人在19号州际公路往北走
on the suspect traveling north
on Interstate 19.
该死
Oh, shit.
罗莉
Lori.
谁？
Who?
我太太
It's my wife.
你已婚吗？
You're married?
应该说我们已分开了
It's safe to say we're separated.
你来开车！
Here, you drive!
疑人已朝第三吊层走
Suspect is headed to suspension level three.
重覆，他已朝第三吊层走
Repeat, he has headed to suspension three.
AV-81，他朝东向威灵顿去了
AV-81,
he's headed eastbound on Wellington.
我要你在他到达之前先到达
收到吗？
I want you there before he is, do you copy?
收到，905
Copy that, 905.
所有车辆和空援请往威灵顿
All vehicle and air support,
proceed to Wellington.
在217区组成路障
Establish a barricade in zone 217.
中央要各单位留在防御区
Central, I want all units
to maintain their perimeter.
将他迫入路障
Drive him into that barricade.
不得给他留下逃走时空
Do not allow him any room for evasion.
清楚吗？
Is that clear?
收到，905
Copy that, 905.
所有车辆准备就绪
All vehicles, hold position.
该死
Oh, shit.
Shit.
警告，车辆行驶时
Warning, mag suspension cannot be
磁锁故障！
无法停止磁力行驶
disengaged while vehicle is in operation.
你到底在干什么？
What the hell are you doing?
你要配上安全带！
You're gonna need your seat belt on!
警告，车辆行驶时
无法停止磁力行驶
Warning, mag suspension cannot be
disengaged while vehicle is in...
安全系统
警告！
启动一应用
车上有锁
They've got a lock on the vehicle.
它们获授权作战吗？
Are they clear to engage?
你获授权作战
You are clear to engage.
- 明白吗 ？
- 不明白！
- Got it?
- No,no!
- 明白吗？
- 明白！
- You got it?
- Yes!
该死！
Shit!
欢迎，操作系统已启动
Welcome. Operating systems activated.
欢迎回家，利特先生
今天好吗？
Welcome home Mr. Reed.
Did you have a nice day?
很好，多谢
Great, thanks.
身份确认：核准
锁匙，锁匙，锁匙
The key, the key, the key.
我录此讯息
This message is being recorded
是为了安全计
in the event of a worst-case scenario.
你肯定很想知道答案
所以我会从头说起
I'm sure you're desperate for answers,
so I 'll just start from the top.
我的姓名是…
My name...
你的姓名是加路孝生
Your name is Carl Hauser.
该死
Oh, shit.
这个录音的互动功能有限
This recording has limited
interactive capabilities.
请重组问题
So, just try rephrasing the question.
你替麦费思工作
You work with Matthias.
是与不是
Yes and no.
但我从未见过那人
I've never actually met the man.
根本没有人见过他
Hardly anyone has.
我知这很复杂
Look, I know that this is complicated.
- 复杂？
- 但这是事实
- Complicated?
- But this is the truth.
我是联邦情报员
I am a Federal Intelligence operative
高克根直接给我下了一道命令
assigned by Cohaagen
就是潜入反动组织杀死麦费思
to infiltrate the Resistance
and assassinate Matthias.
可是
But instead,
我发现自己站错边
I discovered
I was fighting for the wrong side.
我遇上一个女子
I met a woman
她开敌了我的眼睛
She works with the Resistance.
她令我知道我应该为反动组织而战
And she showed me
that they were worth fighting for.
你是指那些恐怖份子
You mean the terrorists.
反动组织不是恐怖份子
Listen, the Resistance are not terrorists.
好的
All right.
麦费思的目标总是军事设施
Matthias' targets are always
military installations.
其他的一切
If there's anything else happening,
都是高克根搞出来
you can be sure it's Cohaagen himself.
相信我
Trust me, all right.
大臣和我相识已久
The Chancellor and I go way back.
打仗时他是我的指挥官
He was my commanding officer in the war.
我清楚知道他的能力
I know exactly what he is capable of.
为何他打自己人？我不明白
Why would he attack his own people?
I don't understand.
他还有什么藉口可以把
联邦机械警力增至三倍？
How else could he justify tripling
production of federal police synthetics?
他在建私人军队，准备侵略殖民地
He is building a private army
capable of invading The Colony.
想一下，好的
Think about it. All right.
殖民地哪种资源是英联没有的？
What is the one resource The Colony has
that United Britain doesn't?
- 空间
- 正是
- S pace.
- Exactly.
他愈来愈不够地方
He's run out of room.
但是即使是高克根本人都很难
But even Cohaagen himself
is gonna have a difficult time
推销这个强夺领土
和迫迁数十亿人的想法
selling the forced seizure
and mass displacement of billions.
所以他把麦费思塑造成敌人
So, he created an enemy in Matthias,
和建立一队军队来对付他
and he built an army to fight him.
但我们可以阻止他，你和我
And now it is up to me to stop him.
Up to you to stop him.
什么意思，我？
What do you mean, me?
机械警察靠生物机械脑干生存
The synthetics run on a bio-mech brainstem.
有个法子可以关掉所有机械警察
All right. Which means, it's possible
to shut 'em all down.
有个歼灭密码
All right, there's a kill code.
是又长又复杂的密码
It's a complex sequence,
但它存在我脑袋中和你脑袋中
but it's in my head, it's in your head.
对不起，再说一次
Sorry, come again.
我去过英联
I went back to U. F.B. territory
想取得密码
to try and retrieve the code,
我很清楚
如果高克根知道我变成什么
knowing full well that if Cohaagen
found out I'd turned,
他会消除我的记忆
he'd erase my memory.
但他不知道我把一个黑盒
But what he didn't know was that
I arranged to have a black box
植入了我脑袋中，你脑袋中
imbedded in my brain, in your brain.
它记录了我看见的一切
It recorded everything I saw.
所以你是说我脑袋里有个小夹万
So, you're saying
there's a little safe in my skull.
对
Yes.
所以我需要你
And that is why I need you.
世界需要你和反动组织重新联系
The world needs you,
to reconnect with the Resistance.
把密码送交麦费思
Deliver the code to Matthias,
让他关掉机械警察
及早阻止高克根
have him shut down the synthetics
and stop Cohaagen while there's still time.
未来全靠你…
The future hangs on what you...
全靠我们跟着怎样做
On what we do next.
老友，祝好运
Good luck, buddy.
你一定是开玩笑
You have got to be kidding me.
这不可能发生
This can't be happening.
我真不该来这儿
Shouldn't have come here.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
我没有选择
I had no choice.
我知道这不容易明白
I know that this is a lot to take.
对，真不容易明白
Yeah, it's a lot to take.
我应该相信吗？
Yeah, I'm supposed to believe this?
那是事实
It's the truth.
孝生，我们一直在找你
Hauser, we have been looking for you.
别叫我…
Don't call me...
我叫杜格拉斯葛
我生于8月29日
My name is Doug Quaid.
I was born August 29th.
母亲养大我
All right, I was raised by my mother.
我十五岁生日前十天她因癌病逝世
She died of cancer ten days
before my 15th birthday.
我二十九岁跟女朋友结婚！
I married my girlfriend when I was 29!
你是生于4月29日的
You were born April 29th.
你由父亲养大
You were raised by your father,
not your mother.
你父亲在你十五岁前撞车身亡
He died before you were 15,
but in a car crash.
相信我，你从未结过婚
And believe me, you were
most definitely not married.
对不起，你知道么？
这些对我都没有意思
I'm sorry. You know what?
None of this makes any sense to me.
我是杜格拉斯葛，我只知道这些
I'm Doug Quaid, that's all I know.
你认识我
You recognized me.
从睡梦中
From a dream.
我从睡梦中认识你
I recognize you from a dream.
那不是梦
It wasn't a dream.
那是记忆
It was a memory.
你想你手上的疤是怎样得来的？
That scar on your hand,
how do you think you got it?
你知道吗？
Do you know?
是工伤
I got it at work.
我当时想帮你逃走
但太迟了
I was trying to help you escape,
but I was too late.
你拉着我的手
You grabbed onto me
有一颗子弹射穿你的手和我的手
and a bullet tore through
your hand and mine.
你一定记得一点的
You must remember something.
你和我，我们…
And you and I, we were...
是
Yeah.
我们要去，我们要去
We got to go. We got to go.
该死，来，来
Shit. Come on, come on.
杜格！
Doug!
哈利？
Harry?
哈利，你在这里干什么？
Harry, what are you doing here?
他们派我来找你
They sent me in for you.
来劝服你
To talk you down.
谁派你来？
Who sent you in?
杜格
Doug,
你不明白
我的意思不是他们派我来这儿
you don't get it.
I don't mean they sent me in here.
我是指他们派我进入你的脑袋
I mean, they sent me into your mind.
我要你听我说
I need you to listen to me.
你患了一种叫偏执分离精神病
You're suffering what's called
a paranoid dissociative break.
是化学幻想创伤引起的
Brought on by the trauma
of a chemical fantasy.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
杜格，你不是真的在此
You're not really here, Doug.
你还在利高公司被绑在椅子上
You're still back at Rekall,
strapped to a chair.
这些全都不是真的
None of this is real.
还在利高公司？
Back at Rekall?
他在说谎
He's lying.
他在说谎！
He's lying!
慢一点
Just slow down.
哈利，你在说什么？
Harry, what are you talking about?
我们在酒吧时你令我担心
所以我跟踪你
When we were back at the bar,
you had me worried. So, I followed you.
我去到时已经太迟
And by the time I got here, it was too late.
你全无反应
You were unresponsive.
他们用化学方法将我渗入你的脑中
So they chemically
transfused me into your mind.
他们认为熟识的脸孔可以令你清醒
They thought a familiar face might
help, to try and bring you back
以免太迟
before it's too late
你会永远无法清醒
and you're trapped here forever.
别听他说，他们只是想套取
你脑中的资料
Do not listen to them. They're just trying
to recover what's in your head.
杜格，我保证
Doug, I assure you.
这不是你认识的哈利
This is not the Harry that you know.
想一下…
Think...
他的声音像他吗？
Does he even sound like himself?
他是安排来防止你出轨的
像你太太一样
He is a plant, just like your wife,
to keep you in line.
我的声音不像我，因为你不想我像
I don't sound like me, Doug,
because you don't want me to.
什么“我不想你像”？
What do you mean, "I don't want you to"?
你要知道
我只是哈利出的主意
You need to realize,
I'm merely the idea of Harry.
其他的都是你的想像
The rest is supplied
by your own imagination.
就算是我现在给你的解释也是
Even the explanation
I'm giving you right now.
全是你想出来的
It's really you. It's really you.
你的脑海选择那些字眼
Your mind is choosing the words.
因为我们在你的脑海里
Because that's where we are, Doug.
In your mind.
我们必须救你出去，否则太迟
We must get you out before it's too late,
and you're trapped here forever.
如果全部在我的脑海里
If this is all in my mind,
为什么你要穿防弹衣？
why are you wearing a bulletproof vest?
因为你替我穿上
Because you put it on me.
- 我替你穿上？
- 你看不见吗？
- I put it on you?
- Don't you see?
解释我怎样替你穿上？
Explain that to me, how do I put this on you?
他疯了
He's crazy.
你的一部份想保护我
Part of you wants to protect me.
以便我引导你恢复神智
To let me guide you back to consciousness
在你的精神病病入膏肓
before your psychosis
reaches such extreme levels
陷入永久昏迷前
that you slip into a permanent coma.
来说服你释放自己
To convince you to free yourself.
孝生…
Hauser...
我是真实的，他也是真实的
I am real. He is real.
他为高克根工作
He works for Cohaagen.
罗莉
Lori?
- 她在这里干什么？
- 杜格，她也在这里
- What's she doing here?
- She's here, too, Doug.
她在这里干什么
What's she doing here?
她在房里，在你身旁
She's in the room, beside you,
她正捉着你的手
holding your hand right now,
十分担心
worried sick.
你感觉到她的存在
It's her presence you're sensing.
她…她想杀我！
She's... She's trying to kill me!
- 不！
- 哈利！
- No.
- Harry!
杜格，那不是真的罗莉
Not the real Lori, Doug.
我告诉她利高公司发生什么事后
她立刻过来
As soon as I told her what was happening at
Rekall, she came straight over.
我要在她上班时打电话通知她
I had to call her at work.
杜格，她爱你的
She loves you, Doug.
哈利，罗莉在晚上不工作
Lori didn't work last night, Harry.
你说谎，你说谎
You're lying. You're lying.
你为何对我说谎？
Why are you lying to me?
只是因为你想我说谎
Only because you wanted me to.
你无法从幻想中自拔
You're clinging to the delusion.
他说谎！
He's lying!
哈利？
Harry?
哈利
Harry.
我可以向上帝发誓，放下枪
I swear to God, put it down.
哈利，你干什么？
Harry, what are you doing?
这不是幻象！
This is not a delusion!
不是？
No?
好吧
Okay, fine.
告诉你
Tell you what.
这些证据还不足够吗？
Is that proof enough for you?
若是真的话我会那样做吗？
Would I have done that if this were for real?
看，我不害怕，杜格
You see, I'm not afraid, Doug.
你也不应害怕
You shouldn't be either.
说够废话了
告诉他真相
That's enough of this bullshit.
Now, you are gonna tell him the truth,
否则我杀了你
or I swear to God I'm gonna kill you.
不要…不要
Don't... Don't.
孝生…
Hauser...
他想令你投降！
He's trying to manipulate you
into giving yourself up!
- 我们要离开这里
- 去哪？
- We got to get out of here.
- And go where?
杜格，你无法摆脱思想
There's no getting
out of your own head, Doug.
但若你让我帮你
你可以逃离这恶梦
But you can escape this nightmare
if you let me help you.
现在帮我吗？
Help me how?
- 别听他说
- 你怎样可以帮我？
- Don't listen to him.
- How can you help me?
别听他说
Don't listen to him.
杜格，你要向她开枪
You have to shoot her, Doug.
什么？
What, now?
我知这令你为难
I know that's asking a lot,
但她是你的
but she's at the epicenter of this whole
扭曲幻象的关键
twisted fantasy of yours.
她代表你所有的失落和不快
She represents all your frustration,
all your unhappiness.
- 孝生…
- 所以
- Hauser...
- Which is why
我们杀她是不要紧的
it would mean nothing if we were to kill her.
要选择重回现实的是你
It's you who has to choose reality.
杜格，向她开枪吧，我答应你
You shoot her, Doug, and I promise you,
你惊醒后会看见我在房中坐在你身边
you will gasp awake
and find me sitting in the room beside you.
那个真实的我
The real me.
- 不
- 你的老友，哈利
- No.
- Your old pal, Harry.
看着我
Look at me.
你一转头便看见你那
Turn, and you'll see your beautiful,
漂亮的太太
loving wife.
杜格，她想你回去
She wants you back, Doug.
我们两人都想
We both do.
杜格，对了
That's right, Doug.
回来
Come on back.
杜格，回来
Come on back, Doug.
我不可以让他们带你走
I can't let them take you away.
抱歉，很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
她当然无法办到
Of course she can't do it.
她不是真实的
She's not real.
现在你只需要向自己证明
Now you just need to prove it to yourself.
杜格，干掉她
End her, Doug.
干掉这恶梦
End this nightmare.
向她开枪！
Shoot her!
该死，杀死她！
Kill her, damn it!
开枪！
Shoot!
老天
Jesus Christ.
哈利，该死
God damn it, Harry!
- 你没事吧？
- 没事
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
来
Come on.
宝贝，你还在吗？
You still out there, baby?
还是我应该称呼你为孝生
Or I suppose I should be calling you Hauser.
我想我成了笑柄
I guess the joke's on me.
我真的以为你是失败者
I really thought you were a loser.
原来我一直
跟最出色的特务一同生活
Turns out, I was living with
the greatest intelligence agent alive.
高克根仍然想你回去
Cohaagen still wants you back, you know.
我想他对你仍有信心
Guess he still has faith in you.
你以前一直是他最重用的
But then you always were the favorite.
但我知你是什么
But I know what you are.
孝生，你是叛徒
You're a traitor, Hauser.
叛徒都要受死！
And traitors get put to death!
来，来
Come on, come on, come on.
也许你想给你的小女友临别一吻
So you might want to give
your little girlfriend a kiss good-bye.
只要她不介意你过去一直吻的是谁
Long as she doesn't mind
where those lips have been.
对了，我要干掉这婆娘
Oh, that's it, I'm ending this bitch.
糟糕，子弹用完了
Shit, I'm out.
来!来！
Come on! Come on!
去！
Go!
等等，等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
来
Come on.
该死
Shit.
去
Go!
那里
There.
该死
Oh, shit.
来
Come on.
把枪给我
Give me the gun.
跟着他
Track him.
抓着我的臂！
Grab my arm!
往下面的吗？
Is this going down?
不？
No?
D-14层
Level D-14.
该死
Shit.
来！来！
Come on. Come on.
等等，等等
Wait, wait.
去！
Go!
你真在行
You really know how to pick 'em.
来
Come on.
接近大臣的人士没有确实或否认…
Sources close to the Chancellor
will neither confirm nor deny...
要乘搭地心车必需出示有效的通行证
Passage on The Fall requires
a current transit visa.
若你有有效的通行证
请前往资讯部
If you do not have a current transit visa,
please visit the information office.
最大的地产代理公司已开幕
请记得到访…
The largest real estate agency
has now opened. Be sure to visit...
反动组织的领袖躲藏了六个多月
The Resistance leader has been
in hiding for over six months.
联邦警方根据
In the wake of these latest attacks,
最新一轮袭击发现了惊人的新证据
federal police have
uncovered alarming new evidence
警戒！警戒！国防威胁级别：红色
证明高克根政府多名官员
长久以来的怀疑是真的
proving what many
in the Cohaagen administration have
麦费思及其恐怖活动是
long suspected, that Matthias
and his terrorist movement
受殖民地总督及其地区组织资助
are being funded by The Colony's governor
and his district's organization.
未经证实的消息指他们
正在作出军事调动
And we're now hearing unconfirmed reports
of military mobilization.
接近大臣的消息人士
Sources close to the Chancellor will neither
- 不肯证实或否认有关报告
- 天啊
-confirm nor deny the reports.
- Jesus.
反动组织领袖已经…
The Resistance leader has been...
我们要送你到麦费思那儿
We've got to get you to Matthias.
怎样可以找到他？
How the hell do we find him?
有法子，来
There's a way. Come on.
他是谁？
Who is he?
他是孝生
It's Hauser.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
嗯
Yeah.
- 我们会通知你爸爸你来了
- 多谢
- We'll let your father know you're here.
- Thank you.
麦费思是你爸爸？
So, Matthias is your father?
你当然记不得，他是
Of course you don't remember that.
Yes, he is.
知道是好事
That's good to know.
施压
气锁已封
Airlock sealed.
高克根每天都在全面搜查英联
Cohaagen scours U.F.B.
和殖民地找寻麦费思
and The Colony every day
looking for my father.
找不到他是因为他不在这些地方
The reason they can't
find him is he's not there.
战争过后
After the wars,
没有人会疯得到这里来
no one would be crazy
enough to come out here.
大家都远离封锁区域
Everyone stays out of the No Zone.
明智
Makes sense.
警告
唏唏
-Hey.
差不多了
Almost there.
你没事吧？
You Okay?
没事，我…
Yeah, I'm...
大家都好像认识我，但我
Everyone seems to know me, but me.
真奇怪
It's strange.
是
Yeah.
我看得出他对这些人很重要
I can see he meant a lot to these guys.
是
Yeah.
他对我们帮忙很大
He gave us the upper hand.
我们有些人可以看见他的最大优点
And some of us were really
able to see the best in him.
如果最大的优点消失了那怎办？
What if the best is gone?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你知道孝生并非完美
Hauser wasn't perfect, you know.
有时可能是混蛋
Could be a real asshole sometimes.
你只不过想令我好过点
You're just trying to make me feel better.
也许
Maybe.
很有效
It's working.
安全
Clear.
他想单独见他
He wants to see him alone.
别走太远
Don't go too far.
好的
Okay.
孝生先生
Mr. Hauser.
你想怎样？
What is it you want?
我想帮你
I want to help you.
你不是为此而来的
That is not the only reason you're here.
我想恢复记忆
I want to remember.
为什么这样？
Why?
我便可以做回从前的自己
So I can be myself, be who I was.
每个人都想寻找真正的自己
It is each man's quest
to find out who he truly is,
但答案是
but the answer to that lies
在当下，不是在过去
in the present, not in the past.
我们大家都是如此
As it is for all of us.
但过去令我们知道今天变成了什么人
But the past tells us who we've become.
过去的事构成人的思想
The past is a construct of the mind.
令我们盲目
It blinds us.
蒙蔽我们
It fools us into believing it.
但内心
But the heart
想活在当下
wants to live in the present.
瞧
Look there.
你会找到答案的
You'll find your answer.
他们说你有资料可以拯救我们所有人
I am told you have information
that may save us all.
别人也这样对我说
I am told the same.
记忆库的防火墙
The firewall to the black box.
进去
We're in.
那儿
There.
看见吗？
You see?
天啊
Jesus.
可以检索出来吗？
Can you retrieve it?
加密了
It's encrypted.
这是什么？
What is this?
麦费思，你好
Hello, Matthias.
你不能想像
You can't imagine how much
我多渴望再见到你
I've been looking forward
to seeing you again.
阔别太久了
It's been far too long.
你真难找
You know, you're a very hard man to find.
- 是陷阱
- 全部关掉！
- It's a trap.
- Shut it all down!
守着所有入口！
Secure all entrances!
走！走！
Move! Move!
去！去！
Go, go, go!
带他走！
Get him out of here!
马上放下枪！
Gun down now!
马上！
Now!
干得好
Well done.
真出色
It's impressive.
你一定有兴趣知道根本没有
You'll be interested to know that
根本没有歼灭密码
there is no kill code.
是假的
It was a fake.
你说谎
You're lying.
对不起
Sorry.
这是找到你的唯一方法
It was the only way to get to you.
大费周章为找一个人
All this trouble for one man.
切勿可氏估一个人的力量
Oh, never underestimate
the power of one man.
我知我不会
I know I don't.
爸爸
Father!
不！不！
No! No!
我们知道总会有这一天
We knew this day would come.
对不起
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
不
No. Melina!
- 中尉？
- 长官，全都在这里
- Lieutenant?
- It's all here, sir.
麦费思的防卫计划
Matthias' defensive plans,
反对组织在殖民地每个哨站的
troop numbers and location coordinates
军队数目和位置座标
on every Resistance outpost in The Colony.
第一波袭击已经展开
The first wave of attack is already underway.
好极
Brilliant.
恭喜，我的朋友
请让他起来
Congratulations, my friend.
Get him up, please.
起来，起来
Up, up, Up.
你办到了
YOU did it.
你是英雄
You're a hero.
你在说什么？
What is that? Modesty? No, no, no.
麦费思死了
Matthias is dead,
殖民地快要瓦解
The Colony is about to fall,
都是多得你
and it's all thanks to you.
我就是知道可以信任你依计行事
I knew that I could trust you
to stick to the plan.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
对，你的记忆不是最可靠
Right. Yours is not
the most reliable of memories, is it?
它很简单
It was really rather simple.
渗透反动力量，找麦费思女儿
Infiltrate the resistance,
find Matthias' daughter.
- 不
- 使她信任你，是
- No. No.
- Get her to trust you. Yes.
对
That's right.
我们一旦发现他是你爸爸
Once we discovered he was your father,
便知道目标是谁
we knew exactly who to target.
马莲娜，他撒谎
Melina, he's lying.
恐怕不是，这也是容易的
I'm afraid not.
You see, that was also the easy part.
因为他诱惑女仔是他的强项
Because seduction has always been
his strongest suit.
但我们要找的始终是麦费思
Still, it was Matthias that we needed to get to.
他需要更多的保证
He would need assurance
far beyond mere words
才会让你这个有前科的人
to let a man with your history, shall I say,
接近他
come anywhere near him.
那时你想到这个聪明绝顶的方法
But that is when you came up
with the ingenious idea
假装被捕和抹掉你的记忆
to feign capture
and let us wipe your slate clean.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
真聪明
It was just brilliant.
还有什么更好的方法
What better way
来说服这老头子
to convince the old man that you
你已经背叛我
had really and truly turned against me.
马莲娜，别听他的
别听他的
Melina, don't listen to him.
Don't listen to him.
- 他撒谎
- 不，我没有
- He's lying.
- No, I'm not.
尽管有少许波折
Granted, there were a few hiccups
例如中途…你闯入
along the way... You popping
利高公司的记忆中枢
your cap at Rekall, for instance.
这不太好
That wasn't good.
就是了
There it is!
昔日的孝生精神
正是你所需要的
The old Hauser spirit.
You're gonna need that.
还有就是你美丽的妻子
And then there was your lovely wife,
她不服从指令
who strayed from her directive.
看着
Look at me.
我们命令她将你活捉
She was ordered to bring you back alive.
我迟些跟你算账
I'll deal with that later.
但是
But,
孝生，是你引领我们到此
you led us here, Hauser.
你帮我们取得这个
You held up your part of the deal,
因此
我会给你第二次机会
and now I'm going to hold up mine.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
- 不
- 你在干什么？
- No.
- What are you doing?
你在…
What are you...
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
你一直计划的
What you and I had been planning all along.
将孝生送进去之前
We made sure to back up Hauser's memory
将他的记忆做一套备份
before we sent him in there.
这是你想要的
This is what you wanted.
不是
- No.
- Yes.
只管想想，几小时后
Just think of it. In a few hours,
你会醒来
you'll awake,
你会再成为昔日的孝生
and you will be the old Hauser once again.
忠心
Loyal
爱国
Patriotic.
无情
Ruthless.
应该怎样处置你？
Now, what to do with you?
我想我们应该保留她
I think we keep her.
别将她卷入此事
Leave her out of this.
I'm in the fucking chair!
我想全世界都很想
I think the world will be very interested
听麦费思的女儿
to hear the confession
忏悔
of Matthias' daughter.
谴责她的父亲和反动组织
Denouncing her father and the Resistance.
去死！
FUCK you!
高克根！
Cohaagen!
看见孝生擅长藉拷打迫人忏悔
You'll be very surprised
to see how good Hauser is at beating
你会很感意外
a confession out of someone.
高克根，去你的
God damn you, Cohaagen.
你捉到我了
You have me.
放她走
Let her go.
放她走！
Let her go!
马莲娜
Melina.
放松点
很快完事，我保证
Just try to relax.
It'll all be over soon, I promise you.
你们很快会团聚的
We'll be reunited very soon.
在这段时间
And meanwhile,
我要领导入侵
I have an invasion to lead.
但愿我能轻易忘记
I wish I could forget that easily.
罗莉
Lori.
发个好梦
Sweet dreams.
夏文，别让他动
Hold him still, Hammond.
混蛋，拜托
Do me a favor, asshole.
尽量反抗
Fight it as much as possible.
这样会更痛苦
Hurts more that way.
夏文，天啊
Jesus, Hammond.
英联的怀疑军队调动报告
Suspected reports of military mobilization
已得到证实
in the U.F.B. have now been confirmed.
但先前以为是铲除
But what was thought to be an operation
恐怖份子领袖麦费思的行动
to uproot terrorist leader Matthias
英联12区现场报导
数千军人集合
appears to be on the scale
of a full military invasion.
似乎是要大举进行军事侵略
有人目睹武装军人登上地心车
An estimated 50,000 armed troops
估计人数有5万
他们准备调派往殖民地
can be seen boarding The Fall,
preparing to deploy for The Colony.
总督对殖民地各区
The governor has issued a level-three alert
英联7区一地心车
即将入侵
发出三级警戒
to all districts of The Colony.
已将最新的任务档案
Have the latest mission profiles
输入所有军人了吗？
been programmed into all our troops?
我们谈时已指派小组指挥官
Being distributed to
all squadron commanders as we speak.
好极，我们什么时候出发？
Excellent. When do we depart?
长官，你一下命令便可以立刻出发
As soon as you give the order, sir.
立刻出发
You have it.
可以找个地方安置她吗？
And find someplace for her, will you?
开始程序
登陆三号海湾
批准进入
三号海湾批准进入
Bay three access granted.
奉命进行代号310行动
We are a go on Code 310.
殖民地的市民全都有敌意
Citizens of The Colony are
to be considered hostile.
将所有机械警察输入
使用致命武力程式
Program all synthetics to use lethal force.
重复，殖民地的市民全都有敌意
Repeat, citizens of The Colony
are to be considered hostile.
奉命进行代号310行动
We are a go on Code 310.
前往殖民地需时约17分钟
Time travel to The Colony:
approximately 17 minutes.
09号运贷海湾
这是阿里士多德8号
再给我车号，讯号不清楚
This is Aristotle 8. Can you give me
that rover ID again? You're breaking up.
你是说9 ？
Was that a nine?
- 你没事吧？
- 没事
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
我们要下车了
We got to get off this thing.
现在
Now.
你爸爸…很抱歉
Your father... I'm so sorry.
- 高克根说的一切…
- 他在撒谎
- All those things that Cohaagen said...
- He was lying.
我不可能背叛你
I couldn't have betrayed you.
我说过我会找你
I told you I'd find you.
我记得，我一生人里
I remember. My whole life,
只有一个记忆是永远记得的
only one memory stayed with me.
他们永远消除不了
They could never erase that.
6号海湾损毁报告
Damage report in bay six.
- 你准备好了吗？
- 准备好了
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
所有紧急人员
All emergency personnel,
请到6号海湾报到
please report to bay six.
准备地心吸力转移
Prepare for gravity shift.
放下武器！
Drop your weapons!
马上！
Now!
Right now!
中尉，我们在第9层
Lieutenant, we've
secured the prisoners attempting escape
捉到企图逃走的囚犯
on level nine.
6号海湾企图逃走的囚犯已经被捕
The prisoner in bay six
was just caught attempting escape.
她跟另一个人在一起
是个男性
She was with a second individual, male.
是他了
That's him.
处理吧
Deal with it.
来
Come on.
还有袋
And the bag.
动手
Do it.
第二组组张，第七层监房…
Team leader two, team leader two.
Seventh level prison...
英联
殖民地
进入地心
Entering core.
没事的
It's okay.
它们处于休止状态
They're in stasis.
是
Okay.
休止
该死
Shit.
注意，在无地心吸力状态下
Attention, emergency hatch cannot deploy
- 紧急仓无法调配
- 你在做什么？
-while in zero gravity.
- What are you doing?
孝生，这些门不开是有理由的
Hauser, these doors don't open for a reason.
我们要等至穿越地心
We'll wait till it passes the core.
然后才能去
Then we go.
该死
Shit.
反地心吸力
Gravity reversing.
来
Come on.
拿着
Take this.
紧急仓已作出调配
Hatch deployed.
开始减速
Commencing deceleration.
去
Go!
- 走！
- 紧急仓已作出调配
- Move!
- Hatch deployed.
开始减速
Commencing deceleration.
它们往上层去
They're headed topside.
什么？
What?
我跟着他们
I'm going after them.
罗莉，不要
Lori, no.
如果他们去到顶层
我会对付他们
If they make it up top, I will deal with them.
必需确保我们到达时这些军队已启动
Just make sure those troops are activated
并且放到殖民地去
and off-loaded the moment we arrive.
不得让孝生阻止这次侵略
明白吗？
Hauser is not stopping this invasion.
Do you understand me?
跟着他们
Follow them.
该死，我们走到了飞机湾
Shit. We got to get to the aircraft bay.
来
Come on.
去
Go.
不！孝生！
No! Hauser!
捉住他！
Secure him!
政府官员已宣布整个殖民地
进入紧急状态
Government officials have issued
a Colony-wide state of emergency.
所有百姓要立刻撤离家园
All civilians are to evacuate
their homes immediately
前往殖民地边境以外
and head to the nearest No Zone shelters
数千军人聚集
最近的封锁区收容站
outside The Colony border.
当局劝谕各人遵照疏散命令
Officials are urging everyone
to comply with the evacuation orders.
继续轰炸反对组织的据点…
Continued bombings
on Resistance holdouts...
地心车停顿
The Fall secured.
3号至87号海湾已经武装
随时可以行动
Bays three through 87
now armed and active.
让它们立刻行动
Let's get them on the move now.
孝生，你真令人失望
You really are a disappointment, Hauser.
我想现在是时候将记忆永久消除
I'm afraid it's time to erase
those memories for good.
再见，老朋友
Good-bye, old friend.
武器系统已经启动
Weapon systems activated.
武器库已清仓
Ammo chamber is empty.
来
Come on.
侦测
- 武器系统重新装弹
- 该死，来
- Weapons systems reloading.
- Shit, come on.
你真的认为那样可以
阻止整个侵略行动吗？
You really thought
that would stop an entire invasion?
不，但这样可以
No, but I think this Will.
物件已辨识
看看你
Look at you.
你还在战斗
You're still fighting
但你根本不知自己是谁
and you don't even know who you are.
我记不起自己以前是谁
I may not remember who I was,
但我知我现在是谁
but I know who I am.
替我跟我太太说声好
Say hello to my wife for me.
来！跑！
Come on! Run!
来，来！
Come on. Come on!
去！
Go!
这是什么？
What is it?
没事的
It'll be fine.
唏，唏
Hey, hey.
唏，醒来
Hey, wake up.
醒来，醒来
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
来
Come on.
来，来
Come on, come on.
唏，醒来
Hey, wake up.
唏！
Hey!
来，醒来
Come on, wake up.
醒来
Wake up.
把你的幻象告诉我们
Tell us your fantasy.
我们会把记忆给你
We'll give you the memory.
别胡思乱想
Don't mess with your mind, man.
不值得呢
It ain't worth it.
秘密特务
Secret agent.
那是你，对吗？
That's you. Right?
嗨
Hi.
Hey.
嗨
你没事吗？
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
我们办到了
We did it.
不
No!
唏
Hey!
你的手没有疤
There's no scar on your hand.
唏，唏！
Hey, hey!
来
Come on!
你以为没有临别一吻
Did you think I'd let you leave
我会让你走吗？
without a kiss good-bye?
“直至死亡把我们分开”
对吗？
"Till death do us part," right, baby?
充电
对了
That's right.
立刻放下武器！
Drop the weapon now!
对，就是他
It's all right. It's him.
先生，你没事吗？
You okay, sir?
- 没事
- 肯定？
- Yeah.
- You sure?
我们在下面有医疗人员
We've got a medic down in here.
老天
Oh, my God.
谢谢你
Thank you.
全殖民地的人都走到街上
People are spilling into the streets
all across The Colony,
庆祝很多人所希望的事终于成真
celebrating what many hope will finally be
殖民地成为独立国
a path to an independent nation.
当大家都害怕的入侵
A new page in history
随着地心车被毁而结束
has been turned
as the invasion so many feared
我们的历史揭开新的一页
ended with the destruction of The Fall,
结束了长时间的经济和政治压迫
a longtime symbol of economic
and political oppression.
现场报导殖民地人民庆祝实况
我们还没有高克根大臣
命运的消息
No word yet on the fate
of Chancellor Cohaagen,
但据悉他跟他的军队一同被歼灭
but we are being told that he perished
along with his forces.
老天
Jesus Christ.
我知
I know.
真难以置信，是吗？
It's hard to believe, isn't it?
喂，那是什么？
Hey, what is it?
利高公司
唏
Hey,
你没事吧？
you all right?
没事
Yeah.
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
肯定？
You sure?